A man's coffin.
A woman's wedding dress.
What a delayed burial.
Waiting to be buried
with his deceased wife.
His fiancée.
He couldn't marry her while alive,
so her dress went into the coffin first.
What a pair of tragic lovers.
Xiao Han!
Xiao Han, what are you doing?
I'm taking the points for this monster.
Are you going to risk everyone's lives
just for your points?
If you don't want to die,
get over here and hold down both sides!
Come a little closer, girl.
Let's huddle together for warmth, okay?
Hurry, stab it in!
Okay!
This thing isn't the target.
The system's clearance task...
That extremely yin object
must still be in this room.
And it's planning to freeze us to death.
How much is your worthless life worth?
If I freeze to death,
your whole family
won't be able to pay for it!
Let go of me! Boss, you can't do this!
Take it off and give it to me!
Your filthy money is worse
than toilet paper here.
If you dare reach out
your dirty paws again,
I'll throw you out immediately.
Okay, okay, let go first.
Just you wait.
What a waste of energy.
Better than someone who won't
even waste a bit of energy
and only cares about his own points.
She looks very weak. Let me see.
No pulse.
Algor mortis accompanied by rigor mortis.
She's been dead for at least two hours.
Bullshit! Why are you cursing her?
You didn't wait for it either.
It's fine, me too.
Honey.
I'm so cold.
Look, she moved!
She spoke!
Huang Kai, let go! Don't touch her!
Every time you touch her,
her zombification speeds up.
If you keep holding her,
you'll personally hold her
as she turns to ashes.
Honey, I'm so cold.
Foolish.
Honey.
Look at me.
I know you haven't enjoyed
a single day of happiness
in the 40 years you've been with me.
Direct all your hatred
and resentment at me.
Your self-righteousness
will not only kill everyone,
but also leave her
without an intact corpse.
This fire can't burn it at all.
It's not the extremely yin object at all.
Old Huang, I told the Bodhisattva
that I hope we can
buy a small house by the sea
in the future.
Watching the sunrise and sunset,
living comfortably.
Okay, I will definitely
give you a good life.
You always made me wait.
I waited until you retired.
Waited until you were free.
Waited until you got old.
Now you finally have time.
But I'm already dead.
Honey,
I-I thought we still had time.
Don't let her touch that talisman!
Old Huang, burn it!
Honey,
don't leave me.
Take me home.
Forty years of obsession
turned her into a vengeful spirit.
Burn that talisman, quick!
Liu Yiyang!
Burn that empty promise and let her go.
The woman in the coffin
waited for Master Ren her whole life.
She was waiting for
the same thing Qin Xue was.
Old man, I'm leaving first.
There are leftovers in the fridge.
Remember to heat them up.
The extreme Yin obsession object
has been destroyed.
Congratulations to the surviving players
for clearing the Nether Mortuary.
We made it out.
We really survived.
We're back in reality.